That the Indian market is seeing a one-fourth
percent jump above 15850 on the screens. At this
time, the business has cooled down a bit. When I
looked before coming in, there was a one-third
jump, now it has become one-fourth, but yes, the
strength of the day,
good recovery from the initial dip, that is the highlight of the time, so let's just
add it here. Machine Sir, hi, good
afternoon, have you given your view on the market
and what are the best picks at this time, the
alligator is very police in the market and I
say that because inflation is not in,
versus rising also, the third indication that
protects it is numbers and guidance and
extremely positive Vengsarkar, Loot Taylor
number to start with HDFC Bank
news-reel and I think Pimpri
Scientifically Insurance Construction Real
Estate, so you tell me where is the temple
visible and you are seeing weakness just starting to take
off, South Travel and
Entertainment is tracking off, so today's
topic is if you say animal tax, please so first
Kayal State General Insurance ICICI
Lombard, height in giving very  Good entry
point is Rs 1525,
take this price and keep a trading stop loss of fifteen hundred rupees,
big dated back to 1595, district Saturn
's half gold was there and a little profit
booking has come but it rings quality
stock to my best price, second solution
I told you yesterday also, I
like it very much at this price, half
your development, its address will be 10%
strongest in the last inverter, so
Norway's stoploss target of 225 at 1313 is
absolutely right, it is a famous temple, the temple has to be
bought from the screen
and now we will make a plinth, you had talked about the
buying perspective, but what are you,
yes brother, 10:30 16 is from President John, it is
doing a great, above that, has it
come down by 10 points, so now this 9
President's f-18 12402 should be done here
that it has to be bought, definitely
buy, now those who want to come on support, then do it, have
both the supports been found, that the
economic is around 15800  If you
get it there, buy it in the tube for tomorrow, I will
wait, I will take it to the
orphan tips today buy take home in the last tennis, so that
means now that fresh once
more, since last week highlighted Meena 15
86000 Jones Pacific, you were stuck many times,
so now you have to buy there after selling a heavy acquisition, then there
is a turn wall and otherwise the strong
support base of this zone is Gavaskar,
if it comes around 15800 then buying is
seen on the upside, then you have to relate it again,
you will be out on the channel, a
call will be given around the project, okay, Naxal issue,
knowledge is being sung, so much weekly, now
show the management on that, Mindtree's
CFO V Ni, your Desai sir will be
seen on your screen, Vinay ji, welcome,
show the results, texture on one screen, on one
side the performance of the stock, then the exchange rate, the
market liked your numbers, listen
to graduation juice and the rest,
their performance is 7.7 percent growth
in I, as many
express stations as sweet from America  You performed better than that,
from where did you
get the help and more importantly, please
explain the breakup, Sir, breakup means
both volumes and realizations would have improved,
how much loot was there in the scooter from
A to Z. First of all, thank you for bringing me on your show
and for giving me this opportunity, as
you rightly said, the performance till date has been
quite good, 7.0 Tomato, for the last several
years we had momentum in Bill Prince,
communications technology and
retail were doing well, in this quarter
you would have seen that the banking
financial services vertical has also crossed over, the
travel vertical is now
recovering gradually, all this together
is quite good momentum, where is the demand coming from,
cloud infrared or data
migration, the customer focus is clearly on the
digital experience, the
way I am reaching our customers,
how fast am I reaching out to the customer so that my
sales are
proper, this is actually a demand maintained
and research in digitization, Dhawan, this
generated train driving direction,
Mohammad Rafi saw that we
Firing in the headquarter is also a good thing, if there is demand then there is
volume and realization is also
good, we have
signed up launch projects in the last two quarters,
its name is going on and its momentum gives
us confidence that this momentum will continue for the next several
quarters, I will
open the support by sidelining all the points of Taurus, the
most important is the speed I liked
and the internal, for example,
why was Devendra seen jumping 3435 percent,
it was seen going above 500 million dollars, so the
traction is great,
Meena, now how will the environment be set
up, how is the deal pipeline, which will
back the orders, will it not be difficult or
not,
this is absolutely a soft wind, it is quite strong
and the pipeline is also doing quite well,
they had said in the last quarter
that we were expecting some part in the banking pension service verticals,
which will be signed in Q4, which is
not that much, it is
quite Moody's wants to be on the side in life,
hence their Make Craft Villa account details
in consumer packaging, so at what time  There is a
very strong momentum in technology
and many other developments are going on right now. The anti-
beans are long-term, the boy is 3, 4 to 5 years old. There is a
lot of work going on on this.
We have a conference that this quarter will also be
decided. This momentum will remain the same. And
in YouTube also, you can clearly see abroad
that this is not your company. Front
vote. Alum cotton and
ghee are performing very softly in IIT. In
between, explain to the MPs what is happening.
Why is this kind of demand, to some extent,
killing the printer on the printer.
What has changed?
How did the wicket happen? This will be the
first time in the world in the last year that the
entire world was shut down at the same time.
Now you cannot go out, you cannot
do anything. Right now people are stuck for a month or two. It is going on for a
few minutes. We do
not know how long it will last. So,
how will you do business in such a period of sustainability? There is
a solution for that, that is Edifice. You are
so digital now.  You will keep
your flexibility, you will keep as much celery as you can, you will
take your flight infrastructure on blouse,
all these things which people might have seen
in the roll of three or five years, they have
completely edited them,
today this situation has come due to the pandemic,
tomorrow there may be some other edition, so people
still